Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Records 5149
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 12 (Box 183, Folder 10)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 23 (Box 183, Folder 11)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 16 (Box 183, Folder 12)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit E (Box 183, Folder 13)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 21 (Box 183, Folder 14)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 22 (Box 183, Folder 15)
- Study of Railroad Motive Power (Box 183, Folder 16)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 24 (Box 183, Folder 17)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 25 (Box 183, Folder 18)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 26 (Box 183, Folder 19)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 28 (Box 183, Folder 20)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 19 (Box 183, Folder 21)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 20 (Box 183, Folder 22)
- Wages - Rules - U.S.A., 1932-1933 (Box 183, Folder 23)
- 1948-49, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 24)
- 1947 (Box 183, Folder 25)
- 1944-46, 1944-1946 (Box 183, Folder 26)
- Yardmen US, 1959 (Box 183, Folder 27)
- 1932-46 US, 1932-1946 (Box 183, Folder 28)
- Circular Letters US mainly re: SUNA, 1951-1958 (Box 183, Folder 29)
- 1950 (Box 183, Folder 30)
- Report of Proceedings in connection with Wage Movement, 1919-1920 (Box 184, Folder 1)
- US RR Administration re: RR Trainmen 28JUL1919 Transcript of Proceedings (Box 184, Folder 2)
- US RR Administration re: RR Trainmen 26JUL1919 Transcript of Proceedings (Box 184, Folder 3)
- US RR Administration re: RR Trainmen 25JUL1919 Transcript of Proceedings (Box 184, Folder 4)
- US RR Administration re: RR Trainmen 24JUL1919 Transcript of Proceedings (Box 184, Folder 5)
- US RR Administration re: RR Trainmen 23JUL1919 Transcript of Proceedings (Box 184, Folder 6)
- US RR Administration re: RR Trainmen 22JUL1919 Transcript of Proceedings (Box 184, Folder 7)
- US RR Administration re: RR Trainmen 21JUL1919 Transcript of Proceedings (Box 184, Folder 8)
- US RR Administration re: RR Trainmen 31JUL1919 Transcript of Proceedings (Box 184, Folder 9)
- US RR Administration re: RR Trainmen 30JUL1919 Transcript of Proceedings (Box 184, Folder 10)
- US RR Administration re: RR Trainmen 29JUL1919 Transcript of Proceedings (Box 184, Folder 11)
- BRT #5446 (Box 184, Folder 12)
- Algoma Central & Hudson Ry. - 40 Hr. Work Week (Box 184, Folder 13)
- Dominion Atlantic Ry. - 40 Hr. Work Week (Box 184, Folder 14)
- Duluth Winnipeg and Pacific - 40 Hour Week - Canada (Box 184, Folder 15)
- Essex Terminal Ry. (Box 184, Folder 16)
- Grand River & Lake Erie & Northern Rys. - 40 Hr. Work Week (Box 184, Folder 17)
- Niagara, St. Catharines & Toronto Ry. - 40 Hr. Work Week (Box 184, Folder 18)
- Northern Alberta Ry. - 40 Hr. Work Week (Box 184, Folder 19)
- Ontario Northland (Box 184, Folder 20)
- Oshawa Ry. - 40 Hour Work Week (Box 184, Folder 21)
- Pacific Great Eastern - 40 Hr. Work Week (Box 184, Folder 22)
- Quebec Central Ry. - 40 Hr. Work Week (Box 184, Folder 23)
- Sydney & Louisburg Ry. - 40 Hr. Work Week (Box 184, Folder 24)
- Toronto, Hamilton & Buffalo Ry. - 40 Hr. Work Week (Box 184, Folder 25)
- Toronto Terminals Ry. - 40 Hour Work Week (Box 184, Folder 26)
- Winnipeg Public Markets RR - 40 Hour Work Week - Canada (Box 184, Folder 27)
- C. N. Ry. (W) - 6 Day Work Week (Box 184, Folder 28)
- Canadian National - 40 Hour Week - Canada (Box 184, Folder 29)
- Canadian National (W) - 40 Hour Week - Canada (Box 184, Folder 30)
- C. N. - 40 Hour Week - Canada (Box 184, Folder 31)
- C. Pac. - 40 Hour Week - Canada (Box 184, Folder 32)
- C. Pac. (W) - 40 Hour Week - Canada (Box 184, Folder 33)
- United States Court of Appeals No. 17,149 (Box 185, Folder 1)
- Rebuttal of BRT to Statement of Canadian Pacific Ry. Copy 1, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 2)
- Rebuttal of BRT to Statement of Canadian Pacific Ry. Copy 2, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 3)
- Rebuttal of BRT to Statement of Canadian Pacific Ry. Copy 3, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 4)
- Rebuttal of BRT before Board of Conciliation and Investigation copy 1, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 5)
- Rebuttal of BRT before Board of Conciliation and Investigation copy 2, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 6)
- Rebuttal of BRT before Board of Conciliation and Investigation copy 3, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 7)
- Casualties to Railway Employees copy 1 (Box 185, Folder 8)
- Casualties to Railway Employees copy 2 (Box 185, Folder 9)
- Casualties to Railway Employees copy 3 (Box 185, Folder 10)
- Elimination and/or Changes in Rules copy 1, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 11)
- Elimination and/or Changes in Rules copy 2, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 12)
- Elimination and/or Changes in Rules copy 3, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 13)
- Elimination and/or Changes in Rules for Yardmasters copy 1, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 14)
- Elimination and/or Changes in Rules for Yardmasters copy 2, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 15)
- Elimination and/or Changes in Rules for Yardmasters copy 3, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 16)
- Diesel-Electric Locomotives - Canadian Pacific Railway copy 1 (Box 185, Folder 17)
- Diesel-Electric Locomotives - Canadian Pacific Railway copy 2 (Box 185, Folder 18)
- Diesel-Electric Locomotives - Canadian Pacific Railway copy 3 (Box 185, Folder 19)
- New Rules and Changes in Existing Rules for Yardmasters copy 1, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 20)
- New Rules and Changes in Existing Rules for Yardmasters copy 2, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 21)
- New Rules and Changes in Existing Rules for Yardmasters copy 3, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 22)
- New Rules and Changes in Existing Rules copy 1, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 23)
- New Rules and Changes in Existing Rules copy 2, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 24)
- New Rules and Changes in Existing Rules copy 3, 1952 (Box 185, Folder 25)
- T/0s-Lineups-Comm. Of Record - General Correspondence (Box 186, Folder 1)
- General (Box 186, Folder 2)
- Decisions - Vacation Committee (Box 186, Folder 3)
- Vacation Agreement, 1941 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  December 17, 1941
- Vacations - Canada (Box 186, Folder 5)
- Carriers' Vacation Policy Under 11/20/64 Agmt. When Preparing Briefs for NRAB, 1964 (Box 186, Folder 6)
- Vacations - Other Organizations (Box 186, Folder 7)
- Union Shop - General (Box 186, Folder 8)
- Check-Off Agreements - Union Shop (Box 186, Folder 9)
- Union Shop Agreement & Certified Mail Agmt. (Box 186, Folder 10)
- Agreement - Canadian Checkoff (Box 186, Folder 11)
- Union Shop Agreement (Box 186, Folder 12)
- Procedure for Processing Union Shop (Box 186, Folder 13)
- Constitutionality Union Shop Rule (Box 186, Folder 14)
- Digest of Union Shop Arbitration Awards (Box 186, Folder 15)
- Arbitration Awards - Union Shop (Box 186, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous - Whitney/Luna Correspondence, 1965 (Box 187, Folder 1)
- Labor Arbitration (Box 187, Folder 2)
- Report of the National Legislative Representative 54-58 Congresses (Box 187, Folder 3)
- Report of the National Legislative Representative 59th Congress (Box 187, Folder 4)
- Report of the National Legislative Representative 60th Congress (Box 187, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous - BRT Memorabilia (Box 187, Folder 6)
- Misc. - Nat'l Conference of RR and Utilities, 1965 (Box 187, Folder 7)
- Misc. Material, 1960-1968 (Box 187, Folder 8)
- Property of Constitution Committees (Box 187, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous re: Unification, 1968 (Box 187, Folder 10)
- Circular Ltrs., 1948-1953 (Box 188, Folder 1)
- Unification Agreement (Box 188, Folder 2)
- Ruling - Re: Switching (Box 188, Folder 3)
- Vol. Assmt. JPK Library & E. Roosevelt Mem. Foundation. (Box 188, Folder 4)
- Vacation Agreements (Box 188, Folder 5)
- Wage & Rules, 1963-1964 (Box 188, Folder 6)
- Can. W&R Movement, 1963 (Box 188, Folder 7)
- Office Instructions (Box 188, Folder 8)
- BRT Misc. (Box 188, Folder 9)
- Circular Ltrs., 1954-1960 (Box 188, Folder 10)
- Traveler's Insurance Company (Box 188, Folder 11)
- Strike Notices, 1970 (Box 188, Folder 12)
  December 10, 1970
- Book #1 Unification Comm., 1968 (Box 188, Folder 13)
- RLEA General, 1946-1952 (Box 188, Folder 14)
- RLEA January, 1965 (Box 188, Folder 15)
- RLEA February, 1965 (Box 188, Folder 16)
- RLEA March, 1965 (Box 188, Folder 17)
- RLEA May, 1965 (Box 188, Folder 18)
- RLEA June Meeting (Box 188, Folder 19)
- RLEA July (Box 188, Folder 20)
- RLEA August (Box 188, Folder 21)
- RLEA September Meeting (Box 188, Folder 22)
- RLEA October (Box 188, Folder 23)
- NRAB 1st Division, 1950-1955 (Box 189, Folder 1)
- Transportation Statistics - Truck-trailer (Box 189, Folder 2)
- Report of E. J. Connors - NRAB 1st Division, 1945 (Box 189, Folder 3)
- NRAB 1st Division, 1948-1949 (Box 189, Folder 4)
- Wabash - Papers sent in by Deputy President R. J. Brooks and his Report (Box 189, Folder 5)
- C&O (Lines South) Submissions to NRAB 1st Division (Box 189, Folder 6)
- NRAB 1st Division, 1947 (Box 189, Folder 7)
- Record of Mobridge - Lodge No. 262, 1920 (Box 190, Folder 1)
  February 14, 1920
- Minutes of Lodge, 1883-1884 (Box 190, Folder 2)
- Individual Ledge - Lodge 540, 1894-1901 (Box 190, Folder 3)
- Original Ledger - Eugene V. Debs - Lodge #1 (Box 190, Folder 4)
- Proceedings - 1st Annual Convention, 1884 (Box 190, Folder 5)
- Grand Lodge, Brotherhood of Railroad Brakemen - Record of Death and Total Disability Claims (Box 190, Folder 6)
- Original Record of Subordinate Lodges Organized - Brotherhood of Railroad Brakemen & BRT (Box 190, Folder 7)
- 5149-1 -- BRT Miller Cartoons - placed in box 198, 199, 200, by size (Box 191)
- 5149-2 -- BRT Miller Cartoons (Box 192)
  - BRT - FP Miller Cartoons (Box 192, Folder 1)
- 5149-3 -- BRT Miller Cartoons - placed in box 198, 199, 200, by size (Box 193)
- BRT Cartoons and Posters (Box 194)
  - BRT - Posters & Cartoons (Box 194, Folder 1)
- BRT Charters, Certificate, BRT Lodge 149 (Box 195)
  - BRT - Charters, Certificate, Lodge 149 (Box 195, Folder 1)
- Stack of BRT Oneonta posters (Box 196)
  - BRT - Oneonta posters (Box 196, Folder 1)
- 1907 Founders and Members hand drawn poster (Box 197)
  - Founders & Members hand drawn poster, 1907 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    Buffalo Founders List w/ Photos
- BRT - FP Miller Cartoons (Box 198, Folder 1)
  removed box 191/Mapcase 14 - and distributed cartoons to 3 boxes, 198, 199 and 200 by size
- BRT - FP Miller Cartoons (Box 198, Folder 2)
  removed box 193/Mapcase 14 - and distributed cartoons to 3 boxes, 198, 199 and 200 by size
- BRT - FP Miller Cartoons (Box 199, Folder 1)
  removed from mapcase 14/box 191 - part of contents are housed here, smaller items are in box 198, larger items are in box 200
- BRT - FP Miller Cartoons (Box 199, Folder 2)
  removed from mapcase 14/Box 193 - smaller items housed in box 199, some larger items housed in box 200
- Membership and Certificate Register + Ladies Auxiliary to the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (Box 199, Folder 3)
  was formerly box 16 (wrapped)
- BRT - FP Miller Cartoons (Box 200, Folder 1)
- BRT - FP Miller Cartoons (Box 200, Folder 2)
- Copies of Oneonta Poster (Box 201)
  - Copies of Oneonta Poster (Box 201, Folder 1)